Did I make myself clear?
Seventh Prince
You know it's always been me protecting you
The one you love is me
If you have any difficulties
You can tell me
But please don't deceive me
You don't need to know
I've been trying to hide it to keep you out of danger
Zhi'an
I'm your husband
How could you mistake me for the Seventh Prince?
I was drunk yesterday
And acted improperly
Please don't blame me
So you choose to keep deceiving me
I almost believed your sincerity
How ridiculous
It seems I've truly wronged my husband
Then let me apologize to you
That day my husband didn't stay to rest
I slept very restlessly alone
Tonight
My lord, you'll definitely stay with me, won't you?
Are you alright?
I'm fine, I can manage on my own
My lord won't let me touch you
Are you still blaming me?
No
You've had too much to drink
Go to sleep
My lord, where are you going?
We've been married for so long
Yet we still haven't consummated our marriage
Don't you want to?
No one is allowed to touch you
Not even me
You're drunk
Go to sleep now
Why won't you take the Dragon Jade?
Zhu Huaijin, if you're just using me for power
I'll end you and we'll both be free
Like this now
What exactly do you want to do?
But whatever you intend
I no longer have the heart to investigate
The road ahead
I'll walk alone
What?
The Dragon Jade is in South Mountain
I'm not entirely sure about the treasure's exact location
I only vaguely remember
It's probably in South Mountain at the border between Nanliang and Beijin
No matter
Dispatch people immediately
Head to South Mountain at once
South Mountain
It's getting dark
We'll rest here tonight
We'll start searching the mountain first thing tomorrow morning
Understood
Why are you picking these weeds?
These are Golden Shore herbs
Snake venom antidote
Gather some just in case
Why wouldn't Zhu Huaichen recognize golden shore grass?
Back in the mountain cave
He used this exact herb to delay the poison's effects for me
Who exactly are you?
How do you know about me?
I...
You could say we're old acquaintances
In any case, I mean you no harm
Oh
This is golden shore grass
It has detoxifying properties
There aren't many medicines on this mountain
Let me apply it for you
Night is falling
I need to find a way out quickly
Enter the mountains to find the princess
Take this with you
It repels snake venom
I need to relieve myself
I'll accompany you
Your Highness, please do as you wish
Call me when you're finished
Alright
In these deep mountains and dense forests
If you get lost
Don't blame me
I really should thank you, Duan Yurou
Zhi'an
Who's there?
Is that my husband?
It's Huaijin
You were caught in a hunter's trap earlier
But you're safe now
Are you following me?
We've found the princess consort
You all go ahead
I'll handle things here
Understood
I didn't mean to follow you
I just noticed you hadn't returned for a long time
And grew concerned
So I followed your trail to check on you
I didn't expect you'd gone so far
This is too dangerous
My husband is the one who should worry about me
You're overstepping your bounds
His Five Minerals Powder addiction has flared up again
If we leave now
He can't do anything to me
This might be my only chance
To contact the remaining Li family forces